Guide to the Mix Collection 1970-2001 (Bulk 1987-2001) MSS 143
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- ACCRETION 2009 - Series XX: 2003
  - Subseries G: Media
    - Footsteps on the Snow, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1851)
      Old number: 03-196
      TRT: 00:01:45
    - Boyskout, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1852)
      Old number: 03-198
      Director: Satterfield, Leslie
    - Little Frankenstein, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1853)
      Old number: 03-199
      Director: Topiary, Samuel
      Distributor: Love Kitchen Productions
    - Blood Relations, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1854)
      Old number: 03-219
      Director: Simms, Jeannie
      TRT: 00:35:00
    - [1] -- Die! Faggot Die [2] -- Happy Valentine, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1855)
      Old number: 03-222; 03-223
    - Buffering, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1856)
      Old number: 03-225
      Director: Hung, Kit
    - My Mother At The Consulate, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1857)
      Old number: 03-226
      Director: Mentlik, Gail
    - Recorder, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1858)
      Old number: 03-235
      TRT: 00:02:30
    - The Hardest Core Porn on the Net, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1859)
      Old number: 03-236
      Director: NG, Fiona
    - How Fluttering, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1860)
      Old number: 03-252
      Director: Kim, Jim Sung
      TRT: 00:04:14
    - Hermishly Yours, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1861)
      Old number: 03-263
      Director: Potter, Susan
      TRT: 00:11:25
    - Finally, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1862)
      Old number: 03-265
    - Security Anthem, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1863)
      Old number: 03-267
      Director: Lambert, Kent
    - Strange and Charmed, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1864)
      Old number: 03-268
    - Let's Get Frank, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1865)
      Old number: 03-274
      TRT: 01:15:00
    - 49 Days in Motion, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1866)
      Old number: 03-275
      Director: Platt, Lisa
    - I am a Boyband, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1867)
      Old number: 03-276
      Director: Nemerofsky Ramsay, Benny
      Distributor: V TAPE
    - Fragment Of An Analysis of a Case of Hysteria, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1868)
      Old number: 03-289
      Director: Rypinski, Sam
      TRT: 00:12:40
    - Operation Invert, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1869)
      Old number: 03-290
      Director: Mateik, Tanya
      TRT: 00:11:20
    - The Singing Forest, Submitted: 2003 (Box 86, Media ID: 143.1870)
      Old number: 03-292
      Director: Ameer, Jorge
- ACCRETION 2009 - Series XXI: 2004
  Submission tapes. Subseries B (correspondence), subseries D (electronic database), subseries F (special programs), subseries H (ticket sales), subseries I (outreach), and subseries J (grants/fundraising) do not exist for this year.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Tape Inventory, 2004 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: Media
    - A Girl Named Kai, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1871)
      Old number: 04-008
      Director: Ling Xue, Kai
      Year: 2004
    - Between the Boys, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1872)
      Old number: 04-011
      Director: Yuzna, Jake
    - Pretty Things, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1873)
      Old number: 04-020
    - The Undergrad, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1874)
      Distributor: Moe Film
      TRT: 00:39:00
    - Martin, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1875)
      Old number: 04-029
      Director: Basquin, Bill
    - Pornographic Apathetic, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1876)
      Director: Cottam, T. Arthur
    - Subway Consciousness, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1877)
      Old number: 04-064
      Director: Koll, Giovanni
    - As American as Apple Pie, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1878)
      Old number: 04-085
      Director: Patterson, Monte
    - clit or dick, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1879)
      Old number: 04-089
      Director: Viefhues, Jasco
    - P.Y.T., Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1880)
      Old number: 04-104
    - The Perfect Match, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1881)
      Old number: 04-106
      Director: Gutierrez, Miguel
    - Trick Saddle, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1882)
      Old number: 04-112
      Director: Rogers, Jenny
    - transparent transparent, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1883)
      Old number: 04-114
      Director: Rosskam, Jules
      Distributor: MamSir Productions
    - Blow You Kisses, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1884)
      Old number: 04-115
      Distributor: Willing Suspension Films
    - In the Dark, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1885)
      Old number: 04-116
    - Behold Goliath or The Boy With the Filthy Laugh, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1886)
      Old number: 04-117
      Director: Kalin, Tom
      TRT: 00:08:30
    - Poster Girl, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1887)
      Old number: 04-118
      Director: Scheurwater, Hester
    - J.-P. (Remix of "Tuesday and I" by Jean-Paul Kelley), Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1888)
      Old number: 04-119
      TRT: 00:06:53
    - Butter Balls, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1889)
      Old number: 04-126
      TRT: 00:25:00
    - Arcade Trade, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1890)
      Old number: 04-132
      Director: Halperin, Samara
      TRT: 00:18:00
    - Carve, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1891)
      Old number: 04-137
    - The Drive North, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1892)
      Old number: 04-138
      Director: Ernst, Tess
      TRT: 00:13:00
    - Imitations of Life, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1893)
      Old number: 04-139
    - Night Swimming, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1894)
      Old number: 04-144
      Director: Killacky, John
      TRT: 00:04:10
    - Mine, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1895)
      Old number: 04-149
      Director: Schrader, Carrie
      Distributor: Lonesome Lady Films
    - Whole-A Trinity of Being, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1896)
      Old number: 04-155
      Director: Shelley, Barry
      TRT: 00:15:50
    - World Trade Opera, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1897)
      Old number: 04-156
      Director: Pelletier, Alain
      TRT: 00:29:30
    - Apocalypse A Go Go, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1898)
      Old number: 04-162
    - Cerrojos (Locks), Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1899)
      Old number: 04-163
      Director: Ceacero, Carlos
      Distributor: Carlos Ceacero Ruiz / Pablo Sanz Garcia
    - Learning Stalls: the amn probe examples, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1900)
      Old number: 04-177
      Director: Darrin, Martin
      TRT: 00:06:20
    - Audition Tape, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1901)
      Old number: 04-184
    - The Sheelagh, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1902)
      Old number: 04-189
      Director: Barbtaylor
      TRT: 00:02:00
    - Eating Regular, Submitted: 2004 (Box 87, Media ID: 143.1903)
      Old number: 04-193
      Director: Patterson, Andrew James
    - Digits, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1904)
      Old number: 04-201
      Director: Rees, William Scott
    - Tilted, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1905)
      Old number: 04-204
    - Quicktime Interruptus, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1906)
      Old number: 04-209
      Director: Andrews, Stephen
    - [1] -- Tan My Hide [2] -- Judy! Judy! Garland! [3] -- Plexus: Real to Real, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1907)
      Old number: 04-250; 04-251; 04-252
      TRT: 61:9:22
    - Carisma (Charisma), Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1908)
      Old number: 04-260
      Director: Planell, David
      Distributor: Prosopopeya Producciones
    - Forward Hand, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1909)
      Old number: 04-267
      Director: Kolmel, Jenn
    - Stone Welcome Mat, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1910)
      Old number: 04-269
      Director: Carducci, Gina
    - Meet My Breasts, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1911)
      Old number: 04-281
      Director: Mallette, Tera
    - I Feel Love, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1912)
      Old number: 04-287
      TRT: 00:14:30
    - Paxi und Fixi (Paxi and Fixi), Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1913)
      Old number: 04-288
      Director: Poklar, Micki
      Distributor: Lightning Media
    - 1974 In California, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1914)
      Old number: 04-317
      Year: 2005
    - Level-C, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1915)
      Old number: 04-319
    - Dreaming Awake, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1916)
      Old number: 04-320
    - Perils Mayhem Mercy, Submitted: 2004 (Box 88, Media ID: 143.1917)
      Old number: 04-321
      Director: Child, Abagail
      Year: 1986-1989
- ACCRETION 2009 - Series XXII: 2006
  This series contains materials pertaining to the nineteenth year of the Festival. Subseries B (correspondence), subseries D (electronic database), subseries F (special programs), subseries H (ticket sales), subseries I (outreach), and subseries J (grants/fundraising) do not exist for this year.
  - Subseries A: Administrative Files
    - Tape Inventory, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Subseries G: Media
    - The Sea Calls Us Home, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1918)
      Old number: 06-037
      Director: Simpson, Annie
      Year: 2006
      TRT: 00:02:15
    - Das Flustern Des Mondes (Whispering Moon), Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1919)
      Old number: 06-043
      Director: Satzinger, Michael
      Distributor: Magic Movie
      TRT: 01:37:00
    - Skyscraper Modern, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1920)
      Old number: 06-044
      Director: Daniel, Todd
      TRT: 00:04:20
    - Pretty Things, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1921)
      Old number: 06-046
      TRT: 00:14:15
    - Dans le passage, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1922)
      Old number: 06-049
      Director: Sity-Fortin, Nathaniel
      TRT: 00:15:52
    - Savoir Aimer, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1923)
      Old number: 06-050
      Director: Lievre, Pascal
    - Patriotic, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1924)
      Old number: 06-051
      TRT: 00:04:03
    - Hold Me, Don't Let Go, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1925)
      Old number: 06-052
      Director: Mariano, Karina
    - Sniff, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1926)
      Old number: 06-054
      Year: 1997
      Distributor: T.O.F.U. Productions
    - XLPIII: Movements East-West, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1927)
      Old number: 06-055
    - XLPII: Mother/Land, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1928)
      Old number: 06-056
    - Mr. Leather, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1929)
      Old number: 06-062
      Director: Garrett, Jason
      Distributor: Feel Good Films
      TRT: 01:10:00
    - 100% Woman, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1930)
      Old number: 06-093
      Director: Duthie, Karen
      Distributor: Video Out Distribution
      TRT: 00:50:58
    - Aus der Leere, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1931)
      Old number: 06-096
      Director: Ruff, Markus
    - Right After They Pet Me, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1932)
      Old number: 06-107
      Director: Higgins, Janene
    - Yo Tengo Fuerza (I Have Power), Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1933)
      Old number: 06-114
      Director: Adebanjo, Olutouin
      TRT: 00:23:00
    - Boys Grammar, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1934)
      Old number: 06-121
      Distributor: Australian Film Television and Radio School
      TRT: 00:07:46
    - Little Spirits, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1935)
      Old number: 06-128
      Director: Condit, Cecelia
      TRT: 00:08:40
    - RESTE-LA!, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1936)
      Old number: 06-163
      Director: Tachou, Frederic
      TRT: 00:11:45
    - Feiern (Don't Forget to Go Home), Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1937)
      Old number: 06-198
      Director: Classen, Maja
      TRT: 00:60:22
    - Dance or Die, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1938)
      Old number: 06-203
      Director: Leija, James
      TRT: 00:10:10
    - The Arousing Adventures of Sailor Boy, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1939)
      Old number: 06-208
      Director: Bisch, Jenny
      Distributor: Winnipeg Film Group
    - CANDY: Super8 Shorts [1] -- En-Wrapped [2] -- Sugah Lips [3] -- Raining Candy [4] -- Swedish Fish [5] -- Bottoms Up [6] -- Untitled [7] -- Dirty Sweets [8] -- Candy Corn Girl [9] -- Caked [10] -- Candy Boyfriend, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1940)
      Old number: 06-209; 06-210; 06-211; 06-212; 06-213; 06-214; 06-215; 06-216; 06-217; 06-218
      Director: Hanson, Anne; Riibe, Leigh; Reynolds, Sarah; Dishman, Tracy; Schaffer, Kirsten; Park, Aaron; Marsak, Lindsay; Weakland, Sean; Carlton, Wendy Jo; Plourde, Jason
      Distributor: 2001 Seattle Lesbian & Gay Film Festival
      TRT: 00:33:20
    - Lucky 7: Super8 Films [1] -- Rainier & Cigarettes [2] -- Lucky 13 [3] -- Fast 'n' Lucky [4] -- Fishing [5] -- I Wonder [6] -- Tough Luck [7] -- My Hands [8] -- Are You The Lucky One? [9] -- Lucky Lefty [10] -- Flock of Seagulls, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1941)
      Old number: 06-219; 06-220; 06-221; 06-222; 06-223; 06-224; 06-225; 06-226; 06-227; 06-228; 06-229
      Director: Costa, Kara; Fagereng, Liev; Romano, Shannon; Baroch, Patrick; Isis Youth Group; Granada, A.J.; Garcia, Xui; Roach, Tanzania; Kennedy, Stephen; Howes, Dawn; Carlton, Wendy Jo
      TRT: 00:36:40
    - Every Wandering Cloud, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1942)
      Old number: 06-251
      TRT: 00:07:00
    - [1] -- Song of the Whoopee Wind [2] -- Beastial Comforts [3] -- Heavenly Figures [4] -- Hell Hole Hostage [5] -- The Wayward Syllabus [6] -- Holiday Hang Ups, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1943)
      Old number: 06-252; 06-253; 06-254; 06-255; 06-256; 06-257
      Year: 2005-2006
      TRT: 01:23:00
    - Pink Shirt, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1944)
      Old number: 06-267
    - Things I'll Never Say, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1945)
      Old number: 06-271
      Director: Le, Caroline
      TRT: 00:29:40
    - Angus Dei, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1946)
      Old number: 06-274
      Director: Finklestein, David
    - Draft 9, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1947)
      Old number: 06-276
      Director: Leventhal, Dani
    - Super8: Nine Worlds [1] -- Mr. McFeely's Rather Wet Package (Mercury) [2] -- Venus is a Boi Girl [3] -- Embracing Mother (Earth) [4] -- Mouth From Mars [5] -- Jupiter: AKA Little Spotty [6] -- Random (Saturn) [7] -- Uranus Can't Get a Date [8] -- Neptune [9] -- Little Pluto's Big Day, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1948)
      Old number: 06-309; 06-310; 06-311; 06-312; 06-313; 06-314; 06-315; 06-316; 06-317
      Director: Lanza, Gus; Blu, Eli Max; Richards, Apryl; Graney-Sauckle, Elliat; Isis Youthcare; Crowe, Harrison; Murphy, Brian; Ohlberg, Jason
      TRT: 00:30:00
    - [1] -- Westward Ho [2] -- 9 is a Secret, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1949)
      Old number: 06-333; 06-334
      Director: Renwick, Vanessa
      Year: 2001-2002
      TRT: 00:07:20
    - Portrait #2: Trojan, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1950)
      Old number: 06-335
    - [1] -- Bahar [2] -- Citizen Lobbyist, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1951)
      Old number: 06-365; 06-366
      Director: Karagoz, Huseyin; Watts, Tim
      Distributor: Canadian Filmmakers Distribution Center
      TRT: 02:24:00
    - [1] -- Rugburn [2] -- A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Funeral [3] -- Valley of the Chapstick [4] -- World's Worst Architecture [5] -- The Boy in the Plastic Bubble [6] -- Une Petite Morte [7] -- Game On [8] -- In Cairo [9] -- Lead Role: Father [10] -- Build [11] -- They Only Come Out At Night, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1952)
      Old number: 06-367; 06-368; 06-369; 06-370; 06-371; 06-372; 06-373; 06-374; 06-375; 06-376; 06-377
      Director: Anderson, Trevor; Barber, Max; Kennedy, Robert; Groves, Cameron; Phelan, Jamie; Cole, Keith; Caffery, John; Vaughn, RM; Raval, PJ; Atkins, Greg; McKinney, Glendon
      Year: 2004-2005
      TRT: 01:58:34
    - Tweak, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1953)
      Old number: 06-393
      Director: Schnibbe, Margie
    - Munchausen, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1954)
      Old number: 06-433
      Director: Oberbeck, Susanne
    - Spawn of Pickerel Ron, Submitted: 2006 (Box 89, Media ID: 143.1955)
      Old number: 06-434
      Director: Maryniuk, Michael